I wonder if the future I saw with you back then will stay that way.
Now, if you want to take care of it...
We'll be waiting for you.
How was life in the shirt?
Great!
I want to see more Life of the Shirt!
I didn't get to it yet.
Uh-oh.
Hold on a second, please.
Wait a minute.
I want to see more shirt life!
Is that possible?
I'm still with you.
I want to be
bejean
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Third hybrid.
That's great! I knew you could handle it!
I wonder if I can manage it?
Oh, no!
How do you feel now?
How do you feel right now?
I don't know if I'm ready or not.
I don't feel like I'm on the ground, and I'm not sure if I'll be able to make a calm face.
It's awkward, but I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best.
So, how was it, Mother?
How was it?
We danced while doing it this time.
It was so hard.
I almost lost heart during the dance.
Like this.
No, but you danced perfectly!
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
What's the matter?
I could barely touch my hands and mouth.
That's right.
I'm enjoying being left out.
You're thinking of inviting me back now, aren't you?
Really? Really?
Hey, look who's here. Yaberty.
Yabatsy, two Yabatsys.
I've got a Yabba-Dee here, too.
It's like your mom's a big seller.
No, it's the other way around, Mom.
She's not selling as well as I thought she would.
Really?
Who said on Twitter that 53 dresses is too few?
Oh, my God.
Yeah, that's right.
How was it?
It was so warm and there were so many people!
But it's my first time speaking out at Hair Wes.
I'm sorry to bother you!
Can we have a picture, please!
Please!
Cute! So cute!
There were so many people wearing Restfull research student T-shirts.
Oh, really?
There were a lot of them.
Thanks for that picture earlier.
Thank you very much.
Please use it.
Oh?
Oh, Simperley.
You sure?
Yes, please.
Let's have a little chat.
Okay, I'm in.
You in? Are you in? Is everybody in?
Is everybody in? Yeah, we're in.
What's the coding for the research students?
Oh, my God. Fingers and marks.
Oh, is that it? California?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
Okay, here we go. Here you go. Cheese.
One more. Here you go.
Okay, thank you very much.
Both for two minutes. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Have a good rest later.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
You look cute.
It looks good on you.
T-shirt.T-shirt.
Cute.
What beauty? You've become something handsome.
Thank you.
You look younger.
Have you lost weight?
Every time I see him, he says I've lost weight.
That's Temple, but no thanks.
Good morning.
You look cute today.
Is something leaking? Your face today.
What's wrong?
It fits me.
Because it fits me?
Because you fit me?
The power of love
The power of long-distance tunamon
Yay
Cute
Excuse me for disturbing you.
It's the execution squad.
Good for you.
Okay, here we go. Cheese, cheesecake.
One more. Cheese.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
He's cute.
It's so weird.
I saw Kazumune here the other day.
It's true, I feel like Osaku has infiltrated.
Weird feeling.
I'm sure he's in on it. I'm sure he's in on it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Yuzuki-chan's favorite song is on there.
Hey, is it okay?
I don't know. Is it okay for you to have a request live? I mean...
It's a normal request live.
Is it okay?
I'm so happy!
I'm looking forward to "Kira Kira Smile"!
Who's number one? Kira Kira Smile.
Number one?
My favorite.
Kira Kira Smile.
No. 2, rock, paper, scissors!
I don't know number 3.
It's got three pops.
Yay!
Looking forward to it.
Good luck. T-shirt on the screen before the show.
This? I didn't really mean it.
What do you think? Here.
Ai-chan's face is so distracted.
It's cute.
What?
I heard it's not selling well, so can I give it some publicity?
If you don't mind.
Thank you.
Get some rest.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you very much.
We'll leave at 8:00.
Sure. The audience will be there.
Cheese and cheese. Thank you.
And a regular two-shot.
May I take a shot of Setoguchi's first union, too?
Yes, let's take it.
Yes, cheese. - Okay.
You don't know where we're at with this.
Everyone?
Self-declared.
Mr. Okanpoku.
Was this everyone's first time in Setoguchi?
Okamoto-san's union, right?
That's for sure.
It's totally your first union, right, Okamoto-san?
Members of Setoguchi's first union
It's our first union, isn't it?
Then, you're in the picture.
A little bit like an artist.
Let's use Dan or Double Board.
Lilpy, it's your first time in Setoguchi, right?
Awww.
May I? Can I take a picture of Asha?
Can I take a picture of Asha?
Can I take a picture of Asha?Asha, can I take a picture of you?
She's so cute. She's just sitting there.
She's so cute, just sitting there.
Mr. Mizukami, are you there?
Yes, I'm here.
Mr. Takagi will take the picture.
Okay.
Keep your eyes on the camera.
I'll take a few pictures.
Lil' P is so cute!
Lil' P is like a drawer.
It's for Lil Pea.
He's so cute!
Customer voice.
Oh, are you okay?
Thank you very much.
I wish I could go to my auntie's.
I want to go to my auntie's.
I'd like to go to Auntie.
The show has finally started!
I'm getting nervous at last.
Good morning.
I'd like to see...
Research students!
Yes, we, the research students of Hokuto Station, are going to perform as "Ultramunk" at the Yukuji room entrance today!
Yes, we are going to perform two of our original songs, "Best & Full Time" and "Onekajito Story"!
In Onekajito Story, there is a part where we say "la-la-la-la-la-la", so let's listen to it together!
That's right.
YouTubers, are you ready?
Yes!
Are you excited?
Who's next?
You there?
Micro!
Micro?
So, Mr. Micro will be next.
Well, you know, the three of you were in the Reclue a little while ago.
And after that, we did a webcast.
Some of you may have seen it.
It seems that they are trying their best to put on their costumes.
I can hear the audience.
And you wear the costume, too.
I'm really nervous.
I'm nervous.
Stay with me.
Stay close to me.
Oh, my God, I might give you a voice.
Thank you very much for your attention.
I'll give you a kiss.
The feelings I've just realized
No words will ever be enough.
How was it?
It was a lot of fun.
I was sad when it ended like it usually does.
I thought it would just be the end.
I thought it was going to be over.
I think it went by so fast, I think it was probably hard on everybody.
Stan Booth and everyone.
It was so sick, wasn't it?
It was very sick.
We're going to have a little more slots for Rumaihurun next time.
Next year?
We'll do it. Next year, I'm sure.
We'll do it next year.
Next year.
It's a big deal.
I'm sure we'll do it.
Let's do it again next year!
Let's do it.
Thank you very much.
The setlist was chosen many times for our Lord.
Thank you so much!
He's been saying how cute and adorable you are offstage the whole time.
I'm so happy.
So, may I ask you one more favor of the Lord?
What is it?
Also, each member of the Batten Girls' Troupe...
You can give Daikoku a cute look, or show off your cute underpants.
Pom-pom-pom to Mr. Daikoku in turn.
That's what this event is all about.
The scoring session is about to begin.
I'm going to use my authority today.
Yes, sir.
You'll line up until you come to the vertical line.
That's how it is, Mr. Daikoku.
Excuse me.I'm sorry, sir.
I'm scared.
Daikoku-san, you can't see anyone when you're standing.
No one can see you in this area.
Patience.
No, no, no, no, no.
Please sit down.
I'd like to show the room enforcer, if you don't mind.
I'm sorry.
If you think you've posed a good look.
If you think you've posed a good look, and if you can appeal to them and put them on quickly...
I'd be happy to come up to your sleeve for a moment.
Then it's time to reward the Lord!
Let the scoring session begin, please!
Partner
Izumi!
I love you.
Suzuki, how many CDs will you give me?
I love you!
I love you, Suzuki!
Excuse me, what time is it?
Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
Well, ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
Let's go, please.
No, just here.
You're not gonna show us anything.
Just here.
Oh, my God, you're so cute.
Oh, my God, it's just cute.
It's just so hot.
That's not good, guys.
You're only doing the big standees from this distance.
Oh, my God, I'm feeling the pressure.
I'm used to seeing that, aren't I?
Good morning.
They're all cute.
Tricue.
A little round, isn't it?
I wonder if they notice. I don't know if you've noticed.
You don't think they've noticed?
You don't know, do you?
You don't know yet?
I'm sure you can tell by the "omamimi".
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'll do my best.
keep up the good work keep up the good work
Attention
go, go, go, go!
I will do my best
We'll do our best, we'll do our best, we'll do our best.
They'll do it, they'll do it.
They'll do it.
[Applause]
Thank you very much for your sense of care for Yuzuki.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for inviting Yuzuki, too.
Thank you very much. It was fun.
Thank you very much.
How was life in a shirt?
Great!
Thank you.
It was a lot of fun.
I would like to see more Life of Shirts.
Not yet.
Please wait a bit.
I'll see you in a minute.
Okay, so it's a real experience.
Is that possible?
As a member of Mr. Shirt,
I was just about to speak.
I'm sorry.
Hold on.
It won't be long now.
Part of the show will be over soon.
It's early.
It's early. When it starts.
I heard it's going to be after this.
Tomorrow, I'm going to Tataniko's in Shibuya.
I'll be there.
Yay, yay, yay!
I look forward to working with you.
Yay, yay, yay, yay!
Well, I was properly received!
Oh, it's Setoguchi-san!
Setoguchi
Gucci Gucci SetoguchiGucci Gucci Setoguchi
Please play the piano for me.
Gucci Gucci Setoguchi
Emcee for me.
Setoguchi
Moderator, please.
That's right.
Okay, we're done here. We're done. We're done.
Thank you very much. Bye-bye.
I look forward to seeing you again today.
Ha-ha-ha.
Bigger and bigger.
Shoemouth together.
It's a song of defeat
I'm scared
What's with the yuzuki salt, I didn't put it in my eyes.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey, Oshio, in the eyes
You look cute today
Scary
You're so good!
He waved at me.
Aww...
Longer than me.
Don't laugh.
That's him.
We've decided on the second part.
That was fast.
Seriously, this whole day is just...
It's early, isn't it?
But, you know... the second part...
The first part is...
I was the host.
I was the host for the first part.
But the second part was a little more...
Nerds?
A nerd.
I think I interfered.
Yes, I think so.
Recently...
I posted it on my Instagram.
I'm a little concerned about
Mr. Tohoku and Amefura-chan
You seem to be listening.
She's been like a little sister to me until now.
But I'm starting to take it more seriously.
I'm starting to push it a little more seriously.
I'm a bit of a nerd.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I feel different from the first part.
It's kind of sunny.
I don't know.
In terms of healing.
In a way.
I've gone a little overboard.
If you have any thoughts...
Yes.
Let's do a set-pat.
You know what?
Rehearsal was terrible.
It was really normal.
Work
and
I kind of got confused with Posey.
It's a little dangerous.
It's no good.
Will you get angry?
Thanks for your hard work.
So, we let Yuzuki and Michitaro be our children.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
It was always my favorite song.
I'm happy.
I'm too happy. You were really sweet from the rehearsal,
And it was perfect.
He remembered it from the beginning.
I'm so glad I pushed him.
I'm off!
So cute!
Cute!
I'm off!
Where are you going to take it?
Here they are!
Yay!
Let's take the road!Let's get out of the way!
This one?
Yes, cheese!
Let's go again!
Yes, thank you!
Yes, cheese!
Thank you!
I've got something for you!
I've been watching you!
Wow!
I'm curious!
Me too!
Congratulations!
It's hard!
Subscribe to my channel!
Good night.
We're all tired now.
Thank you very much.
Sorry, I have to watch it again.
That was good.
That was bad.
You guys saw it, right?
Here.
Right here.
Here, here.
Here.
here
Next notice
Thank you so much!
It's over!
Yes!
All that's left is the crunch.
It's OK.
We're done.
Our mission is over.
It's over for me today, too.
I'm glad it's over.
Now all that's left is the Wilderness Festival.
Wilderness Festival
After time
It's like an after talk
Let's go.
Let's go!
I'm off.
Cheese.
Thank you for watching.
You're taking a lot.
Good for you.
Hands?
I'll take it.
I'm scared.
I was scared last time.
I'm in!
- Good luck!
- I'll pay for it myself.
- I can't let you get out.
- I've already had dinner with my seniors.
- Then it's...
- It's a first.
- No going out with anyone else until then?
- Okay, I won't go.
- Please protect me.
- Okay, okay, I'm here. I'm here, sweetie.
- Yay!
- I haven't eaten at all. I think I might be in a bit of trouble.
- I forgot I'm having dinner tonight.
- Oh, my God, I'm in trouble.
- I'll do my best.
I'll do my best anytime.
Thank you for watching.
Listen to this.
The perfect song for you.
In a sea of stars
In that place where you spent so much time
I dreamed of you, I dreamed of you, I dreamed of you, I lit up your dreams
The innocence of your heart
Was echoing all around.
I remember it all over again
I still want to sing with you now
It's gonna be so big
Come with me
I swore I'd grab you, I swore I'd scatter the lala lala nubbins all over the place.I swore I'd grab it and scatter Lara's navi all over it.
Wow, you're really into this.
Hey, you're hot.
But, Mr. Ogura...
It's not enough.
Not yet. That's what I thought.
Right?
Speaking of Yuzuki's hair festival, that song.
Yes.
Can I have a bite?
Then, please call out the title already.
Yuzuki's Hair Fest, everyone.
This is really the last song.
Are you ready for some fun?
Yeah!
Can you dance?
Can you scream?
Yes!
What an enjoyable life!
Thank you for watching!
Hello, my friends!
I would like to share with you a store bought ichiri that watches my videos alone
A mg a stall
I want to pick you up
Public law addiction
Lose yourself in the juicy blues
the day has come for me to meet you
I'll be moist and full of flavor
the meat is so soft and juicy
I don't care about feelings
Today we'll squeak squeak squeak together
I'm so happy to see you
Cu-cu-cu-cu
Oh, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I can't believe I cried because it was so good.
I'm a girl.
Surprise me.
Cu-cu-cu-cu.
It's your fault.
Oh no no no no
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
Hey, look at me.
You look like this.
Eat me.
I'm your love child.
Tori-tori-tori.
Puripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuri
Tri-tri-tri
If I am reborn
I will find you.
I'll find you. I'll find you.
I don't care how you feel
Today, we're going to squeak together
From oden to lunch to cu-cu-cu-cu
AIIIIIIII foooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
It's delicious, and the tears are just the right amount
I'm a girl
We're all in this together
When you've done your best, you're ready to go
Aye-aye, fo'oo'oo'oo
No matter how hard the day is
I can live on, you give me a smile
Because I'm your girl
Let's spread it to the world Kumami
You're more than just Elicious
No matter how the times change
There's something here that will never change.
But there are days when I feel like I'm going to be crushed
Because...
ApMob
Thank you very much.
It's been fun.
It's great!
Great!
Great job, guys.
I'm going to see this at Soma Lights. This.
I'm sure you will.
Maybe everyone here will see it.
It was cool. The way Macky was wearing it.
It's amazing. It made me want to wear it.
But Izumi, who was taking the pictures, was just wowed.
I don't think so.
I'm looking forward to seeing it later.
Please look forward to it.
Now, Mr. Ogura.
Yuzuki's Ear Festival has come to an end,
May I introduce today's performers again?May I once again introduce today's performers?
First of all,
Due to time constraints, the opening acts for both parts have been limited to the older ladies and the younger ladies,
But in fact, there are 13 of us!
We are all members of "Shimomura Genki Mitsuru"!
Applause!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Genki, please come out again.
Please come out again.
And they enlivened the event with very cool dances and powerful performances.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
And Sugata will be with us again as a vocalism.
It was everyone from Ikuta Korifuji.
Thank you very much.
That was the shortest style. Thank you very much.
And they made both the first and second parts of the event a lot of fun.
Mai, aka Naito,
Mai, a.k.a. Mai Tomono-chan.
Thank you very much. Rumpin.
Thank you very much.
And us.
We
We.
Who's who? Who's we?
Team shot!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
And that's everyone from the second part of Mizuki's ABS!
Thank you very much!
Thank you.
Oh, Mizuki.
I have an emergency fair the day after tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
AmeFlash.
There's someone on the show.
The dreamer.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
So, the day after tomorrow, Yuzuki's Room
I'd like to recap the Yuzuki's Room festival with Ameflash-chan.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
All of you folk fans, all of you surprise researchers, and all of you lupins.
Also, please come visit Yuzuki's Room again, as soon as you can now.
I'm off.
Let's go home.
Please close your room then. Thank you very much.
Thank you all for a really wonderful day.
Can I call you all Yuzuki's room festival family now?
May I?
Well, that's all for now, so we are Yuzuki's Room Festival Family.
I would like to end.
I'm going to go now.
That's all for now, Yuzuki's Room Festival Family.
And everyone else too. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Eh!
Heh heh heh.
Your voice is so loud.
I was surprised when it was over.
You're so loud!
Wow!
Thank you so much for your hard work!
Energy
You accomplished both the first and second parts!
Eh, it was kind of normal fun!
It was so much fun!
All of my favorite kids came out, so
It was a lot of fun.
On the contrary, I'm sad that it's over.
I'll do my best for the next year so that we can do it again next year.
But I'm a little afraid of the heavy rain.
So we don't want to have it blow in June this time.
Let's do it in summer!
Thank you very much!
Thanks to all of you!
I can also put on this handy camera and project it on my apple!
You can hear the water being filled in.
If you can't see your apple, you can take a picture of it from a mirror in your home.
Please subscribe to our channel!
[ED
Please subscribe to our channel.Please subscribe to our channel.